Hey, you 뭘 보니? 내가 좀 sexy, sexy 반했니?
Yeah, you 뭐 하니? 너도 내 kiss, kiss 원하니?
월, 화, 수, 목, 금, 토, 일, 미모가 쉬지를 않네
머리부터 발끝까지 눈부셔 빛이 나네
Oh 저기 언니야들 내 fashion을 따라 하네
아름다운 여자의 하루는 다 아름답네
이 party에 준비된 birthday cake
태어나서 감사해 everyday
I don't need them 그래 내가 봐도 난
looks so cool looks so sexy like kim kardashian
looks so cool look so sexy like kim kardashian
looks so cute looks so pretty like Ariana
이 파티에 준비된 블루 샴페인
태어난 걸 축하해 everyday
I don't need them 그래 내가 봐도 난
3, 2, 1
Queen card I'm hot
My boob and booty is hot
Spotlight 날 봐 I'm a star star star
Queen card I'm top
I'm twerking on the runway
I am a queen card
You wanna be the queen card
I'm a queen card
Take a photo
자신감 넘치는 girl
Queen card
I am a queen card
You wanna be the queen card